

MATTIE BARTON

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACTS

+49 176 3611 7408

maitlandbarton@gmail.com

Karl-Marx-Str. 15, Berlin

in /mattiebarton

EDUCATION

MASTER OF SCIENCE, Human Resource MGMT + Organizational Behavior Lingnan University Hong Kong SAR 2018-2019

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, Supply Chain & Information Management College of Charleston, Honors Charleston, SC, U.S.A 2014-2018

BACHELOR OF ARTS, International Studies College of Charleston, Honors Charleston, SC, U.S.A 2014-2018

EXPERTISE

- Communication & Listening
- Data Analysis/Presentation
- Time Management
- Conflict Management
- Node.js
- Express.js
- React.js
- Javascript
- HTML/CSS/Bootstrap
- SQL / Trevor / Metabase

SUMMARY

Fullstack Software Engineer (MERN stack) with a passion for developing meaningful and high-quality products. With 3 years of past experience as a Client Success Manager, I have developed a holistic understanding of the various stakeholder perspectives (i.e. business and end-user) involved in producing great software. I am ready to take this expertise to an engineering team, where I can have a direct impact in building an excellent product!

EXPERIENCE

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP

Ironhack School S.L.

- Technologies used: React.js, Express.js, Node.js, MongoDB, Bootstrap, Tailwind
- Delivered 3 projects ranging from a game built with basic Javascript, HTML, CSS to a full-stack application built with React
- Developed collaboration skills in regard to building software, teaming up with different classmates to produce 2 of the projects
- Link to projects on github

CLIENT SUCCESS MANAGER

UPPER Technologies GmbH, Berlin | JULY 2021 - Present

- Entered as the first CSM and developed the function from scratch with full ownership
- Strategically involved Solution Engineers and Talent Success Managers to tackle our clients' needs as efficiently and effectively as possible
- Collaborated closely with the Product team for the ideation of UPPER's Client App, translating voice of the customer directly into our product features
- Spearheaded the push to make Sales & CS teams more data-driven, aiding in the setup
 of complex dashboards, additional metric tracking, and bi-monthly CS reports

CLIENT SUCCESS MANAGER

Honeypot GmbH, Berlin | OCTOBER 2019 - JANUARY 2021

- Onboarded and managed 70+ SMB accounts, delivering individualized attention to each client based on unique tech recruitment needs and company culture
- Developed and maintained positive long-term relationships with main contacts, primarily Heads of Product Teams and CTOs
- Analyzed portfolio data pulled from the platform to make informed and customized plans to bring the greatest value to our clients
- Launched various process improvement initiatives formed on client feedback, to ensure that user requests would directly impact rollout of new product features
- Left early 2021 due to Covid-related mass layoffs